

Macedonian Loc. Gal, 13 - Bocenago (TN) 7 March 1993 +39 340 894 76 41

BIOGRAPHY

I'm a 25 years old IT student from the mountainous place of Bocenago, Italy. Living here since I was 6 years old. I have 5 years of working experience in various positions in a building company and I am very interested in web development. I love sport, especially playing football and tennis and I also like watching movies, reading and drawing.



aj0715@live.com

https://alezen9.github.io/



https://github.com/alezen9/



https://linkedin.com/in/aleksandargjoreski-8879a6108/



https://codepen.io/alezen9/

EXPERIENCE

MASON

Costruzioni Edili Gjoreski Vlado | 2010 - 2015

Laborer, mason and sometimes foreman helped me improve my working skills such as speed, efficiency and organization.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER (hobby/spare time)
2018 - Present

Recently I was fascinated by the world of the webapps. I started learning by myself how to use the most modern tools for web development such as Node.js, React.js, and others meanwhile i was improving my skills in other programming languages i already knew. To keep it short, I have done several projects by myself and most of them are on my Github profile.

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Istituto di Istruzione Lorenzo Guetti | 2008 - 2012
Diploma as Quantity Surveyor, learned to use AutoCad and other technical instruments such as theodolites and GPSes.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE

University of Trento |2015 - Present

IT student, did a lot of group projects for both coding and prototyping. Learned a lot of coding languages but most importantly I learned how to approach new ones in order to understand them quickly.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Born in Macedonia. Lived in Italy since i was 6. Learned spanish and english in college and with friends.







SPANISH basic



SKILLS (indicatively)

Html 4/5

Css 2/3

Javascript

Pug (Jade)

Node js

React js

P5 js



